{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Video streaming website YouTube was purchased in it&#039;s entirety by Facebook for US$1.65 billion in stock.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Big the Cat is a playable character in &quot;Sonic Generations&quot;.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Bulls are attracted to the color red.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Adolf Hitler was a german soldier in World War I.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The names of Tom Nook&#039;s cousins in the Animal Crossing franchise are named &quot;Timmy&quot; and &quot;Jimmy&quot;.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "California is larger than Japan.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Television",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In Battlestar Galactica (2004), Cylons were created by man as cybernetic workers and soldiers.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "&quot;Minions&quot; was released on the June 10th, 2015.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In Rugby League, performing a &quot;40-20&quot; is punished by a free kick for the opposing team.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In the &quot;S.T.A.L.K.E.R.&quot; series, the Freedom faction wishes to destroy the supernatural area known as  &quot;the Zone&quot;.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    }
  ]
}